

YAROSLAV PASHINSKIJ

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Greetings! My name is Yaroslav, I am 23 years old and I actively learning and developing in the frontend development.

At the moment I am looking for a suitable vacancy that will provide me with a rapid growth and decent pay. I am a goal oriented and hard working person. I got my skills in this direction by working in my previous company, as well as passing various courses and self-development.

SKILLS

- Javascript, ES6+
- ReactJS, NextJS, Redux, ReduxToolkit
- Typescript
- HTML5, CSS3(Sass / Scss / Less) / Bootstrap
- Three.js
- REST API
- Version Control, Git, GitLab
- Adaptive and Cross-Browser Development
- Debugging

CONTACT

+38 (067) 886-72-75

yaroslav.pashinskij99@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/pashinskij99

https://github.com/pashinskij99

https://t.me/pashinskij99

EXPERIENCE

2020-2023 Frontend Developer | Unilimes

May 2020 - March 2023 (3 years) Odessa, UKR

- Adaptive cross-browser layout of websites and landing pages
- · Creation of sites on React, NextJS, ThreeJS
- Implement new app components according to the design;
- Modify and update existing components' visuals in accordance with the design;
- Most of the projects required the use of 3D models and graphics, for these purposes I used the ThreeJS library
- Fix bugs and improve existing code, application performance, and usability;
- Teamwork was done using GitLab
- Uploading applications to Amazon server (AWS) using pm

EDUCATION

O.S. POPOV ODESA NATIONAL ACADEMY OF TELECOMMUNICATIONS

2016 - 2021 | TELECOMMUNICATIONS

SOME OF MY PROJECTS

https://namastatedev.wpengine.com/

https://pashinskij99.github.io/

https://spotify-clone-eight-lake.vercel.app/

https://wibe-studio-two.vercel.app/

https://subjects-one.vercel.app/

https://components.d1m1kz90x59nht.amplifyapp.com/

https://ferrovial-web-experience-827b81bed2b600.webflow.io/